=== SubitoSMS ===
Contributors: subitosms
Tags: sms, gateway, subitosms
Requires at least: 3.5.1
Tested up to: 3.7.1
Stable tag: 1.2
License: GPLv3
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html

Send SMS texts to all your WordPress web-site's registered users in one click!

== Description ==

SubitoSMS WordPress Plugin lets you send SMS texts to your WP web-site's registered users, connecting to your SubitoSMS.it account.
It also modifies the basic WP user's registration form, adding a field for the user's mobile number. 

== Installation ==

Installation is simple as a standard Wordpress Plugin.

e.g.

1. Download SubitoSMS-v1.x.zip file and upload to wordpress using Plugin menu 
2. Install from Wordpress Plugin's repository searching for SubitoSMS

== Frequently Asked Questions ==

= Are the SMS Free ? =

Unfortunately not, but we provide very cheap SMS prices.

= Do I need to signup ? =

Yes, registration is free and you can test with some free SMS messages.

== Screenshots ==

1. Registration form will be extended in order to allow users to add their mobile phone number
2. Send menu will allow to send a message to all users that are registered and entered their mobile
3. Settings are very simple, username/password and the sender you want the user to see as from.

== ChangeLog ==

= 1.2 =
* First public release